I'm
The motherboard is humming. The processor is
bright. Running a million calculations in the
night. The standard cable's crossed. The audio
is cut. But the system isn't broken. The doors
are never shut. I've got a different kind of
signal to send.
I need a voice to push the volume high A set of
speakers reaching to the sky I'll point the way,
you amplify the sound We lift the heavy metal off
the ground Right in the center of the board A
single point to strike the chord We are the
output for the silent code Navigating by the
crimson node Yeah, we are the Crimson Lord
Locked into the Crimson Lord
Locked into the chassis, the custom-built
machine The fastest architecture that you've
ever seen My hands are on the controls, I'm
steering through the wire Translating all the
static into electric fire I'm running the world
without a single word
I need a voice To push the volume high A set of
speakers Reaching to the sky I'll point the way
You amplify the sound We lift the heavy metal off
the ground Right in the center of the board A
single point to strike the chord We are the
output for the silent code Navigating by the
crimson node Yeah, we are the Crimson Note
Some people don't listen to the static in the air
They miss the massive symphony that's playing
over there
But if you read the data and you understand the
spark We'll light a neon fire In the middle of the
dark
Right in the center of the board A single point to
strike the code We are the output for the silent
code Navigating by the crimson node
The center point We are the voice The crimson
node